=Demon Emperor's Little Matchmaker=
= صانع الثقاب الصغير للإمبراطور الشيطاني =
=Episode 18=
= الحلقة 18 =
Why don't you carry on?
لماذا لا تستمر؟
This is unfair to you.
هذا غير عادل بالنسبة لك.
Chuchu.
حلمات.
I, Li Wuyou, want to declare to the Three Realms
أنا ، لي وويو ، أريد أن أعلن للعوالم الثلاثة
that I want to marry you.
أريد أن أتزوجك.
Wuming.
ويومينغ.
Mother.
الأم.
Are you looking for me?
هل تبحث عني؟
Are you
أنت
planning to sneak into the courtyard again?
تخطط للتسلل إلى الفناء مرة أخرى؟
No.
رقم.
I was going to see
كنت سأرى
Father in the Imperial Study Room.
الأب في غرفة الدراسة الإمبراطورية.
I wonder what magic potion
أتساءل ما هي الجرعة السحرية
Qiao Chuchu gave to your father.
أعطى Qiao Chuchu لوالدك.
Recently, he treats the monster
في الآونة الأخيرة ، تعامل مع الوحش
entirely different.
مختلفة تماما.
He's completely another person.
إنه شخص آخر تمامًا.
Mother, we're family.
أمي ، نحن عائلة.
Who's family with him?
من عائلته؟
He's a half-man, half-demon monster.
إنه نصف رجل ونصف شيطان وحش.
Keep your distance from him.
حافظ على مسافة بينك وبينه.
That monster
هذا الوحش
is born with a curse.
ولد بلعنة.
Because of him, your elder brother died as a baby.
بسببه ، مات أخوك الأكبر وهو طفل.
Wuming.
ويومينغ.
You're the only son I have left.
أنت الابن الوحيد الذي تركته.
You must protect yourself.
يجب أن تحمي نفسك.
If
إذا
anything bad happens to you,
أي شيء سيء يحدث لك ،
I...
أنا...
Wuming.
ويومينغ.
I've invited Lady Ding over to admire the flowers.
لقد دعوت السيدة دينغ للاستمتاع بالزهور.
Let's talk next time.
لنتحدث في المرة القادمة.
This lad.
هذا الفتى.
Could he have a lover now?
هل يمكن أن يكون لديه حبيب الآن؟
I'm hoisted by my own petard.
أنا مرفوع من طرف خبزيري الخاص.
No way.
مستحيل.
I must figure a way
يجب أن أفكر في طريق
to punish this girl who doesn't know the rules.
لمعاقبة هذه الفتاة التي لا تعرف القواعد.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Go back to sleep if you're tired.
عد للنوم إذا كنت متعبًا.
But I want to stay with you longer.
لكني أريد أن أبقى معك لفترة أطول.
Then I'll sleep with you.
ثم سأنام معك.
But didn't you say that you'll wait until
لكن ألم تقل أنك ستنتظر حتى
we're married officially before we...
نحن متزوجون رسميا قبل ...
What are you thinking about?
بم تفكر؟
I'm talking about sleeping.
أنا أتحدث عن النوم.
What did you think?
ماهو رأيك؟
However,
لكن،
if you can't wait any longer...
إذا كنت لا تستطيع الانتظار أكثر ...
No.
رقم.
We...
نحن...
No, no rush.
لا ، لا داعي للاندفاع.
I have no rush.
ليس لدي التسرع.
Don't sleep.
لا تنم.
Let's chat.
دعنا نتحدث.
Do you want to hear some fun stories of immortals?
هل تريد أن تسمع بعض القصص الممتعة عن الخالدين؟
Sure. Are your stories real?
بالتأكيد.  هل قصصك حقيقية؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
The paparazzi of Nantianmen Magazine is my best friend.
المصورون من مجلة Nantianmen هو أعز أصدقائي.
From Jade Emperor of Lingxiao Palace
من اليشم الإمبراطور لقصر Lingxiao
to the Horse Protector,
إلى حامي الخيول ،
I know all about
أعرف كل شيء عنه
their gossips.
ثرثرةهم.
Tell me a story that you find
أخبرني قصة وجدتها
the most fun.
الأكثر متعه.
Everyone says that
الجميع يقول أن
the relationship between Mr. Matchmaker and Taibai Jinxin
العلاقة بين السيد Matchmaker و Taibai Jinxin
isn't good at all.
ليس جيدًا على الإطلاق.
Everyone thinks that's
يعتقد الجميع أن هذا
because their eight characters don't match.
لأن شخصياتهم الثمانية غير متطابقة.
In fact...
في الواقع...
In fact it's because they used to like Flower Fairy
في الواقع ، هذا لأنهم اعتادوا على حب زهرة الجنية
when they were young.
عندما كانوا يافعين.
But Flower Fairy liked Maori Xingjun.
لكن زهرة الجنية أحب الماوري Xingjun.
Isn't that funny?
أليس هذا مضحكا؟
It's quite funny.
إنه مضحك للغاية.
I'll tell you another one.
سأخبرك بواحد آخر.
I think
أظن
today isn't suitable for too many jokes.
اليوم لا يناسب الكثير من النكات.
Lest we may not be able to fall asleep.
لئلا نكون قادرين على النوم.
Some other day perhaps.
ربما في يوم آخر.
You're right.
أنت على حق.
Teach me how to write.
علمني كيف أكتب.
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
The two of you.
انتما الإثنين.
Can you pay more attention in the daytime?
هل يمكنك إيلاء المزيد من الاهتمام في النهار؟
There's a poor and sad person here.
هناك شخص فقير وحزين هنا.
Wuming.
ويومينغ.
Isn't there a saying,
أليس هناك قول مأثور
"You have to strive for your happiness"?
"عليك أن تسعى جاهدة من أجل سعادتك"؟
I know.
أنا أعرف.
But her heart is made of stone.
لكن قلبها مصنوع من الحجر.
There's no use no matter how hard I try.
لا فائدة مهما حاولت.
What are you talking about?
ما الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Be simple. Talk in a simple form.
كن بسيطا.  تحدث في شكل بسيط.
Chuchu.
حلمات.
♪The wind of the early summer♪
رياح أوائل الصيف ♪
♪Created a starry sky♪
♪ خلق السماء المرصعة بالنجوم
♪The dream in my heart♪
الحلم في قلبي ♪
♪Froze at the street intersection in the morning♪
تجمد عند تقاطع الشارع صباحا
♪I've passed the end of the galaxy♪
♪ لقد اجتزت نهاية المجرة
♪I've seen the crowded traffic♪
♪ لقد رأيت ازدحام المرور ♪
♪In my mind♪
♪ في ذهني ♪
♪Your smile is engraved♪
♪ ابتسامتك محفورة ♪